export const week7Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Software Design",
    question:
      "is a process to transform user requirements into some suitable form, which helps the programmer in software coding and implementation.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Software Development",
    question:
      "refers to a set of computer science activities dedicated to the process of creating, designing, deploying and supporting software.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "â€¢	Requirements analysis and design tools",
    question:
      "will be used by software development organizations for requirements analysis of new software.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Code development tools",
    question: "The tools, such as code editors and compilers, are employed",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Configuration Management (CM) tools",
    question: "for military and aerospace program and projects.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Commercial off-the-shelf (COTS) documentation tools",
    question: "include standard word-processing and graphic development tools",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Software Reuse",
    question:
      "the process of creating software systems from existing software rather than building software systems from scratch.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Peer Reviews",
    question: "to find and correct as many errors as possible",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "peer review verification",
    question:
      "methods identify software bugs, errors, and defects for removal with recommendations to improve code development. ",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Concurrent software design/development",
    question:
      "which is a technique to reduce the time to improve productivity.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Lean software design/development",
    question: "it is far more effective to have small working teams",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Concurrent software design/development",
    question:
      "method does make it possible to delay commitment until the last moment when failure to make a decision eliminates an important alternative or decision. ",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "Lean software design/development",
    question: "objective is to move as many changes as possible. ",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "Lean",
    question:
      "is a framework that aims to provide a new way to think about how to organize human activities",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answer: "Agile Models",
    question: "are more effective than the traditional models",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    answer: "Agile process",
    question:
      "method for team efforts reflects how a team of software people works together.  ",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    answer: "Agile Method",
    question: "is also about continuous incremental delivery of products",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    answer: "Configuration management",
    question:
      "is a systems engineering process for establishing and maintaining consistency of a product's performance",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    answer: "CM",
    question:
      "disciplines aim to trim the process and provide more automation in the tools",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    answer: "CM",
    question: "is a support discipline to the Agile team",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    answer: "Software Standards",
    question:
      "It is and will always be a requirement that software design engineers follow required software standards",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    answer: "Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI)",
    question:
      "provides the best opportunity to address software design or development with ongoing support to customers after delivery.   ",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    answer: "CMMI",
    question:
      "does provide a systematic, disciplined approach to all software engineering tasks in the affected program and projects. ",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    answer: "CMMI version 1.3",
    question:
      "coverage will add updated information currently supported by Lean and Six Sigma and customer satisfaction for software design/development life-cycle tasks. ",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    answer: "Six Sigma methodology",
    question:
      "attempts to reduce process variation, resulting in fewer errors and defects.",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    answer: "Software Defect ",
    question:
      "is defined by customer requirements, whether formally documented or an expectation that is not met.",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    answer: "Six Sigma process",
    question:
      "does show fewer defects per opportunities or zero defects in a software work product.",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    answer: "Define, Measure, Analyze, Improve, and Control",
    question: "In Six Sigma, the steps are:",
  },
];

export const week8Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Software Requirements",
    question:
      "Identifying and defining software requirements begin with reviewing the functional or performance requirements developed to identify the constraints on software. ",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "System Requirements",
    question:
      "are allocated to software evaluations determines accuracy, completeness, and applicability of the requirements for work product.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Requirements Analysis ",
    question:
      "Includes step-by-step analysis process to develop requirements for work products. ",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Use Case",
    question:
      "Developed to describe a flow of operations for the performance of systems and software implementation.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Operational Cases",
    question:
      "include functionality, performance, maintenance, and support considerations, as well as the work products operational environment, including boundaries and constraints. ",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Function",
    question:
      "Analyzed to ensure an accurate and complete understanding of what software is expected to perform ",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Architecture",
    question:
      "Graphical representations are prepared and take the form of data flows and software component diagrams.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Integration",
    question:
      "The integration of requirements is the transformation of a functional architecture into optimal design solutions. ",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Verification and Validation",
    question:
      "Each requirement is identified, and a list of techniques include analysis, inspections, demonstrations, and test conducted in software integration facilities.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Requirements Documentation",
    question:
      "It includes software requirements and related information generated, including use cases and derived software requirements, which are the source of each requirement.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Functional Configuration Audit",
    question: "systems, software, documentation, facilities, etc.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Physical Configuration Audit",
    question:
      "formal review that determines if the system met its documented requirements",
  },
];

export const week9Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Errors",
    question: "can appear that were previously undetected.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Bam Theory",
    question:
      "approach is to attempt nonscheduled software integration and testing.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Control",
    question:
      "must be maintained between multiple tests running at the same time. Lack of control can cause chaos",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Development Facility (DF)",
    question: "is normally established for software integration activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Software Tools",
    question:
      "used for integration and hardware units installed are placed under configuration control.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Verification steps",
    question:
      "ensure tests provide a check of the capabilities of software and hardware units.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Test",
    question: "are executed to fix software bugs and errors.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Software Integration",
    question: "is the first phase before any stage of systems integration.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "validation",
    question:
      "concept ensures that the correct work product is the right product to validate. The quality team roles are to perform",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Software Testing",
    question:
      "is the process of evaluating and verifying that a software product or application does what it's supposed to do.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Software Integration",
    question:
      "is the process of bringing together various types of software sub-systems so that they create a unified single system.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Evaluation",
    question:
      "of upgrades includes considering integration problems detected, problems solved, and impacts on software integration efforts.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "Software Integration",
    question:
      "It is the practice of connecting and unifying different types of software parts or sub-systems.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "",
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of quality team? ",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answer: "Architecture Reviews",
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of quality team?",
  },
];

export const week10Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "CMS Team",
    question:
      "focuses on identifying and managing changes and maintaining software configuration and documentation visibility.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "None of these",
    question:
      "Which of the following task is NOT related to software construction and configuration control? None of these",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "ClearCase",
    question:
      "software tool provides an open architecture to implement configuration management and control solutions.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "VOB (Version Object Base)",
    question:
      "is a data repository where files, directories, and data are stored.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Software Data",
    question:
      "refers to the incorporated files/documents in the physical media such as .doc, .txt, .exe, etc.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "ClearQuest",
    question:
      "This software tool provides support for change request management processes and is a complementary tool for ClearCase.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Administrator",
    question:
      "manages the database, coordinates, and provides software inputs to program and project changes.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Software plans",
    question:
      "and process procedures provide the information to coordinate the required review boards to maintain records.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Review board",
    question:
      "is established for software teams to review and disposition changes that affect controlled software and related documentation",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Database Management",
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT involved in the review board members?",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Physical Software media",
    question:
      "(i.e., disk units, CD, DVD, hard drives, etc.) identification and media labels must also be in accordance with the program and project documented media requirements in affected plans.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Configuration Management",
    question:
      "is a systems engineering process for establishing and maintaining consistency of a product's performance, functional, and physical attributes with its requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "Configuration manager",
    question: "Familiar with change and control processes ",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "Lead",
    question: "Responsible for schedules and assignments",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answer: "Software design engineer",
    question: "Makes changes to files under configuration control",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    answer: "Build engineer",
    question: "Utilizes software build concepts and tools",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    answer: "Architect",
    question: "define models",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    answer: "Configuration manager",
    question: "set up configuration management environment",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    answer: "SCM lead",
    question:
      "assign and schedule work activities and define written software configuration management policies",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    answer: "Software design/developer",
    question:
      "make changes to files/directories and deliver software to build engineer",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    answer: "Build Engineer",
    question: "builds components for established baselines ready for test",
  },
];
